var quizArray = [
    {
        question: "1 + 2 = ?",
        options: ["1", "4", "2", "3"],
        answer: 3
    },{
        question: "5 + 19 = ?",
        options: ["32", "30", "24", "50"],
        answer: 2
    },{
        question: "23 - 8 = ?",
        options: ["12", "15", "21", "19"],
        answer: 1
    },{
        question: "5 * 4 = ?",
        options: ["20", "25", "15", "26"],
        answer: 0
    },{
        question: "3 + 2 * 10 = ?",
        options: ["32", "30", "23", "50"],
        answer: 2
    },{
        question: "2 + 7 - 8 * 4 = ?",
        options: ["23", "-23", "-32", "-21"],
        answer: 1
    },{
        question: "15 * 6 + 9 * 5 = ?",
        options: ["312", "142", "123", "135"],
        answer: 3
    },{
        question: "23 * (41 + 86) = ?",
        options: ["2921", "3314", "1452", "3882"],
        answer: 0
    },{
        question: "5.837 / 9 = ?",
        options: ["0.7146", "0.8234", "0.6486", "0.505"],
        answer: 2
    },{
        question: "(914 - 298) * 6.14 = ?",
        options: ["3983.83", "2958.143", "3782.24", "5523.831"],
        answer: 2
    }
];